{
    "subject": "resource/Ramot_Menashe",
    "predicate": "property/foundation",
    "object": "1948",
    "human_readable": "Ramot Menashe was founded in 1948.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9806947708129883,
            "question": "If Ramot Menashe was founded in 1948, what significant event might have occurred that year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9386217594146729,
            "question": "What happened in 1948 related to Ramot Menashe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9385358691215515,
            "question": "When was Ramot Menashe founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8633094429969788,
            "question": "What is the founding date of Ramot Menashe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7850532531738281,
            "question": "What year marks the establishment of Ramot Menashe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7697423696517944,
            "question": "In what decade was Ramot Menashe founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7372117638587952,
            "question": "Was Ramot Menashe founded before or after World War II?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6377237439155579,
            "question": "What can we infer about the history of Ramot Menashe based on its founding date?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5144093036651611,
            "question": "Is Ramot Menashe a recent or historical settlement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3271561861038208,
            "question": "How old is Ramot Menashe?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ramot Menashe was founded in 1948.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5831_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Ramot Menashe a recent or historical settlement?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5831_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can we infer about the history of Ramot Menashe based on its founding date?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5831_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Ramot Menashe founded before or after World War II?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5831_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5831_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5831_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5831_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5831_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5831_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5831_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5831_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5831_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5831_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5831_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that \"Kibbutz Ramot Menashe was founded in 1948\" and \"In November 1948, the kibbutz adopted the name Ramot Menashe\", which supports the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"Ramot Menashe is a kibbutz in the Northern District of Israel with a population of 680 people. The kibbutz was founded in 1948.\" This supports the statement that Ramot Menashe was founded in 1948."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}